Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
It's been about a month
since Chinatsu Senpai
started living with us.
Good morning.
My eyes have gotten used
to her dazzling aura.
I washed your gym uniform,
so don't forget to take it.
I used to hit the snooze button
about five times,
but lately, I've been stopping
after about two.
Having a crush
is so wonderful!
BLUE BOX
EPISODE 4
IF HE WINS
Thank you for the meal.
You have your match tomorrow.
Yup!
You're in a good mood.
I guess I'm just fulfilled every day.
You seem to have settled down quickly.
You know, a boy and a girl,
living under the same roof,
I'm surprised nothing's happened so far.
That's because...
CHINATSU KANO
SORRY TO BOTHER YOU!
Chinatsu Senpai!
DID YOU TAKE MY UNIFORM BY ACCIDENT?
KANO
I HAVE GYM FIFTH PERIOD...
I have to take this to her!
I'LL BRING IT TO YOU!
WHERE SHOULD WE MEET?
SOMEWHERE SECLUDED WOULD BE BEST, RIGHT?
HOW ABOUT THE AV ROOM?
ROGER THAT
I was in such a rush this morning.
We can't have anyone see us.
I need to do this quickly.
Yo, Taiki.
Why are you avoiding me?
It's not what you think.
This is perfect.
Come practice with me.
Sorry! I'll make it up after school!
He ran away.
AV ROOM
This room is usually empty.
Taiki.
Hina! What are you doing here?
RHYTHMIC GYMNASTICS MEETING
We're holding a rhythmic gymnastics
team meeting.
What?
You need something?
Not particularly.
- You dropped--
- Stop!
KANO
Listen, don't touch that.
Why not?
Hey.
Hey, hey.
Well, to be honest,
I haven't washed that since last summer.
- Get out of here.
- Okay.
Hold on, Taiki.
You were wearing your gym uniform
in gym class.
If you haven't washed it
since junior high...
The truth is, I've been wearing it
without ever washing it.
Be gone.
Okay.
Honestly.
Why are there people everywhere?
At this rate, Chinatsu Senpai
will have to wear my uniform.
INOMATA
There's no time left.
CHINATSU KANO
NEW MESSAGE
"Come to the west side of the roof"?
NO TRESPASSING
You're here.
Thank goodness we were able to meet up.
How do you have a key to the roof?
I borrowed it from my friend
in the astronomy club.
Here.
Thank you. You're a lifesaver.
So this is what Chinatsu Senpai
is like at school.
It's nothing.
Crap! You have to hurry,
or you'll be late!
What are you doing?
I thought I'd change here
because there's no time.
Here?
Don't worry.
Girls in athletics learn
to change anywhere.
We're trained to.
That's not the issue!
I'll make sure nobody comes up here.
Sorry.
I've said this before,
but she's way too defenseless.
Does she not understand how cute she is?
Crap!
These sounds are making me imagine things!
- For real?
- So then...
All done.
You okay?
Ten more seconds,
and I would've been a goner.
Ready to go?
You go on ahead.
Okay.
Thanks.
Getting changed right in front of me...
That must mean
she doesn't view me as a guy.
I need to work on that.
Good practice.
Did someone grab the shuttlecocks?
What time tomorrow?
Taiki!
You've got regional prelims tomorrow?
Make sure you don't get all worked up
and embarrass yourself.
Mind your business!
I'll make sure Kyo films it.
So I've been wondering...
Not even a little.
That right?
She's right, though. Don't get worked up.
You have me for doubles,
so that's a guaranteed win.
He's so confident!
You just need to finish in the top 16
in the singles next week.
I'll be fine!
I'm a lot better than before.
I'll even make it
to the top eight or four.
Well, just so you know,
you forgot your racket bag.
Why didn't you mention it earlier?
I wondered when you'd notice.
I'll be right back!
Taiki! Make sure you pack your uniform!
And don't forget your shoes and racket!
They're already packed.
Seeing Mom like this,
I understand where I get it from.
How many towels do you need? Eight?
I don't need any!
I've already packed everything I need.
Really?
Taiki!
- Laundry!
- Gimme a towel!
Here!
Hurry!
Get it together.
I know it's your first high school match,
but it's not your first rodeo.
Why are you so nervous?
Calm down.
Don't go out there and lose
because of some stupid mistake.
There's nothing to feel pressured about.
Exercise to clear the mind!
You're going to nationals, right?
Get it together!
You're practicing this late?
Chinatsu Senpai.
I decided to do some practice swings
to move my body.
Taiki.
Your shirt's inside out.
Okay, I might not be fine.
Sorry!
She didn't seem to care
about changing in front of me.
But this she minds.
Taiki.
Yes?
I didn't know you had a six-pack.
That's what it was?
I guess you do work out a lot.
That reminds me.
Haryu said your body was coming along.
Just because I got a little muscle
doesn't make me better at badminton.
Wow, talk about humble.
Taiki.
What is it?
Hyakue.
What?
It's a pressure point on your head.
It can help you relax.
There's no point in running around
the day before.
You've already put in the hard work.
So stop overthinking things
and go show them what you can do.
Got it?
Yeah.
Okay, this pressure point
really works.
Besides,
you still have next year
and the year after.
The year after?
But that's after you graduate.
You'll be even stronger than you are now.
That's not good enough for me.
Good night.
Okay!
Let's go!
Looks like you got over your nerves.
I don't have time to be nervous.
Well, good for you.
The doubles matches are about to begin.
ROUND 1
Out!
ROUND 3
ADVANCED TO BEST 16
- Huh?
- What?
I mean, it's going so smoothly.
Like we're not gonna
make it out of regional prelims.
You have me, dummy.
Please sign the match sheet.
Although it's painfully clear
what you need to work on.
He's right. These were real games
and there were so many instances
where he covered me.
He's so loud.
Such a bold playstyle too.
Or so I thought, but he's calculated.
One more down.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Harry Senpai?
If it isn't the former KTS Junior member
Kengo Haryu.
Sorry, wrong person.
You crook!
Do you know him?
He used to be my doubles partner
in my junior days.
Meet Shimotomi High's Shoichiro Kishi.
He called you a crook.
I have no idea why.
That's because Harry Senpai
broke his promise.
You said you'd give me
Chinatsu Kano's number!
What?
I said if you beat me.
But I did.
In an official match.
Do you know Chinatsu Senpai?
Yeah.
How could I forget that fateful day
last year at Eimei's school festival?
SCHOOL FESTIVAL
My wallet's gone!
It was a limited edition!
Excuse me!
It was like my favorite idol
popped out of my wallet.
What anime is that?
Don't humor him.
After that, I heard she was friends
with Harry Senpai,
so I asked for an introduction.
But he never came through.
Isn't he awful?
You agree with me, right?
Nice job, Haryu Senpai.
Which is why today,
after I crush you in the doubles,
you'd better introduce me to her!
Kishi.
I don't feel too well.
I think I'm dying.
Yokoyama!
Lucky you already made it past
the prelims.
Fine, then!
We'll settle this at next week's singles!
I'm not playing in that.
When's your next official match, then?
The prefectural qualifiers in June.
June?
I'll find a sub, and we can play now!
- No way.
- I won't leave until you do!
Okay, fine.
I'll give you her number if you beat Taiki
in the singles next week.
More accurately,
I'll ask her if it's okay.
You can't just volunteer me!
Taiki?
My doubles partner over there.
This is a lock!
What should my first message be?
Be careful.
He's better than he looks.
What a jerk!
How did I get roped into this?
I don't like the idea of Kishi getting
Chinatsu Senpai's number either.
Doesn't mean he should just volunteer me.
That's right.
That's Chinatsu Senpai's voice.
It feels a little awkward to see her now.
I'm sure she didn't like
my attitude yesterday.
I'm the one so hung up on going
to nationals this year.
I'm so glad Taiki won.
Well, he has been practicing hard.
He swings his racket at home
instead of studying.
So he'd better win.
And I made tonkatsu
for him today to celebrate.
It'd be awkward if he lost.
Honestly, I was a little worried
that he's pushing himself too hard.
He's got two more years,
so what's the rush?
Yes.
I said that to him too.
That he still has next year and the next.
But then his attitude changed.
It was strange...
Isn't he always?
Shut up.
No, I understand why he'd get mad.
I mean, it's like I was saying
that he was free to lose this year.
I only realized it after.
That's true.
But I was just a little sad
about being reminded
that I'm a year behind her.
It's not like you meant it that way.
Of course not!
Then don't worry about it.
I know, but...
Part of it was me realizing
how quickly this year has gone by.
When I think that I only have a year left,
I got a little envious of Taiki.
I didn't say that to encourage him.
I was just expressing my own insecurities.
And I regret that.
Chinatsu.
You're such a nice girl.
That's not...
So pure!
I'm back!
Welcome home!
Congrats.
Thanks.
You got a good doubles partner, huh?
That's not all of it.
Besides,
I'll win my singles matches too!
You don't have to yell.
I'm going to put my stuff away.
Such a busy boy.
If she's feeling insecure,
that's all the more reason I can't lose.
Where does he get all that confidence?
You honestly don't have to worry
about what you said.
No.
I could learn from his example.
Good luck to you.
Rock, paper, scissors!
They're so fired up.
They're only determining who serves first...
Anyway, I heard you put some weird stakes
on this match.
Don't worry.
I won't tell him
if she doesn't want me to.
Chinatsu Senpai
might be too nice to say no.
Besides, I think Taiki's going to win.
What?
Obviously, since I'm the one training him.
In fact, if he loses,
I'll put him through hell.
Shudder!
GIVE YOUR ALL
I'm glad I'm not his doubles partner.
First game. Love-all.
Play!
Still, his smashes are powerful.
He's good at putting his weight behind it.
You can't just return them.
There you are.
What's up, ladies?
What're you doing here?
We had a practice game
against Kita High next door.
We came to check out the tournament.
Is anyone playing?
My doubles partner.
Oh, him? Let's cheer him on.
Is it because we came?
He can't get any attacks off.
Are you one of those people
who think figure skaters fail their jumps
when you watch?
It's probably his strategy.
His strategy?
It takes time to get used to the speed
of someone's smashes.
Taiki's slow at repositioning.
So he's playing defensive at first
to tire out his opponent.
If you look carefully,
his shots are keeping his opponent moving.
The kid's gotten pretty smart.
Match number 15...
I should get going.
Good luck.
Not going to watch up close?
I'm fine here.
So, actually, I know your situation.
Taiki told me.
He said he trusts you.
Okay, she is cute.
There's something nerve-racking
about tournaments.
Each shot feels heavier.
Did you know?
This game has your phone number
on the line.
And just so you know,
Haryu Senpai's to blame.
So take it up with him.
It's just that Taiki
gets nothing for winning.
So,
would you take him to the aquarium
or something if he wins?
We can't use the gym tomorrow anyways,
so there's no practice scheduled.
Besides,
you're part of the reason
he's so motivated.
I doubt I have that much influence on him...
Yeah, you do.
She stayed behind in Japan
by herself to make the nationals!
She practices first thing
in the morning! So will I!
He's easily swayed.
He's always been stubborn.
Once he makes up his mind, that's it.
But even as a friend,
I can say he's been doing well lately.
The old him wouldn't have been able
to pick up those shots.
I'm sure that part of it
is because he has someone close
with the same goals
to keep him disciplined
and motivate him to put in the effort.
So, if he's able to achieve
some good results,
I think he deserves some kind of reward.
Yes!
He's fired up.
Okay.
If Taiki wins, we'll go to the aquarium.
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm